/** The questions that will form the basis of practiceQuestions, questions, and answers during development. */
export const practiceQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'By area, which country is the considered the second largest in the world, to Russia?',
    category: 'Geography',
    answers: [
      'Azerbaijan',
      'Canada',
      'United States',
      'Russia',
      'China'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Canada'
  },
  {
    question: 'The characteristic color of a shiny coffee thermos is designed to prevent heat loss by which of the following processes?',
    category: 'Heat Exchange',
    answers: [
      'Convection',
      'Radiation',
      'Slow Diffusion',
      'Conduction',
      'Circulation'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Radiation'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which native Denakk\u2019e name for the Alaskan peak Mount McKinley means \u201cThe High One?\u201d',
    category: 'Location, Location',
    answers: [
      'Yukon',
      'Kenai',
      'Denali',
      'Kuyokuk',
      'Whittier'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Denali'
  },
  {
    question: 'While humans have recently accelerated the greenhouse effect, which mostly non-human created gas ' +
      'contributes most to this process?',
    category: 'Got Some Gas',
    answers: [
      'Water vapor',
      'Ozone',
      'Carbon Dioxide',
      'Nitrous Oxide',
      'Chlorofluorocarbons'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Water vapor'
  },
  {
    question: 'The largest object in our asteroid belt, named after the Roman goddess of agriculture, is the namesake ' +
      'of which chemical element?',
    category: 'Astronomy, Chemistry, and Mythology',
    answers: [
      'Cerium',
      'Iridium',
      'Plutonium',
      'Samarium',
      'Palladium'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Cerium'
  },
  {
    question: 'This modern crop is a domesticated teosinte developed by early Mesoamericans which can be found in foods ' +
      'such as nshima, chicha, and angu\u2026',
    category: 'Monocots',
    answers: [
      'Rice',
      'Sugarcane',
      'Maize',
      'Wheat',
      'Millet'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Maize'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which city-state, located on the west bank of the Tiber River, is renowned for its basilica and obelisk?',
    category: 'Autonomy',
    answers: [
      'Monaco',
      'Qatar',
      'Liechtenstein',
      'Vatican City',
      'Kuwait'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Vatican City'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which opera by Gioachino Rossini features Figaro, a tonsorial artist who resides in one of Spain\u2019s ' +
      'largest cities?',
    category: 'Figaro! Figaro! Figaro!',
    answers: [
      'Carmen',
      'The Marriage of Figaro',
      'The Magic Flute',
      'Don Giovanni',
      'The Barber of Seville'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'The Barber of Seville'
  },
  {
    question: 'The architectural period developed during and named after the reign of an iconic royal figure of the late' +
      ' 19th century is\u2026',
    category: 'Architecture',
    answers: [
      'Georgian',
      'Art deco',
      'Victorian',
      'Edwardian',
      'Federal'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Victorian'
  },
  {
    question: 'This Newbery Medal winner is a bildungsroman about a boy and an abused dog who form a bond in West Virginia\u2026',
    category: 'A Bildungsroman',
    answers: [
      'Bud, Not Buddy',
      'The Giver',
      'The Whipping Boy',
      'Shiloh',
      'Holes'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Shiloh'
  }
];
